welcome to manolife online
tap into a world where every day is
better
get back on track and reinstate your
policy with Manulife online
Step One log into your account
policy you want to reinstate
on the policy information tab tap
reinstate your policy now
[Music]
step two download and fill out the
non-med form
foreign
[Music]
proceed to reinstate your policy
step 3 click on choose file to upload
your filled out non-med form in a valid
government issued ID
[Music]
then tap on next to proceed with the
payment using your debit or credit card
regain control of your future reinstate
your policy now with Manulife online
[Music]